All right, we are in Hiroshima.
Right now we are at the Peace
Memorial Park.
We're gonna spend our first two
days here in Hiroshima,
exploring the essential spots here.
And also we're gonna go to
Miyajima Island.
Right now the weather is horrible,
it's wet, it's cold, it is windy.
So we decided to have an easy museum
indoors type of day.
But a lot of the structures here
are also outdoors, so
you can't really avoid the weather here,
unfortunately.
But we did spend a good two hours in the Peace
Memorial Museum that tells sort of
the story of some of the
survivors and the
tragedies that unfolded during
the bombing.
Very strong imagery, probably shown a
little bit of that in this video.
So if you do decide to visit, just
be prepared for that.
There's some really intense images.
I think we're heading to the castle right
now, the Hiroshima Castle.
And don't know if it's gonna be any
better because of the weather, but
we're gonna try to make the best of it despite
the rain and everything like that.
And that's how travel is
sometimes really.
So let's get to it.
All right, we just had a very, very filling
Okonomiyaki at the Okonomimura,
which is the Okonomiyaki Village.
Essentially four floors of small shops
that only specializes in Okonomiyaki.
We decided to dine at Atom.
There's also another one called Momotaro that
I heard a lot of good things about.
Yeah, it's pretty decent experience,
very filling.
We had to order one each, so it was a little
bit too much food than what we're
used to, but all good, all
good, all good.
When the food is good, then it's
all good, in my opinion.
So let's move on to the shopping street,
which is right next door, basically.
We just arrived via the ferry
here at Miyajima Island,
which is not that far from
Hiroshima City.
Just an hour train ride and
ferry ride in total.
And we arrived there, what's
the time right now?
8 in the morning?
Around 8 in the morning.
And yeah, not a lot of people
here yet, but
I expect it to be fully packed
by around 10.
Right now we are heading towards the
shrine, and then afterwards,
hopefully we could go a little trip up
a cable car, get a little view.
There's a lot of clouds right now, so I'm
not sure if we're going to
see anything or not.
So you might be wondering why is the
camera so smooth right now?
Is it some voodoo stabilization magic?
It's not, it's actually a new camera
that I received from DJI.
It's the Pocket 3.
It's a small portable camera.
I always wanted to get the
Pocket 2, but I
was happy to hear when DJI
released a new one,
the Pocket 3, and they were
kind enough to
send this one over for me to test out for
this trip in Japan.
And I'm super excited to see what
I can capture with it.
It's like a small compact camera, and I
think it's great for like when
you're in a crowd
or there's a lot of people and you
don't want to disturb anyone.
So I'm thinking like restaurants,
ramen shops.
We tested out at the Okonomiyaki restaurant,
and that was great.
It was great to have like a
little small camera.
When you're filming with a small camera,
nobody really cares.
They just think you're a tourist or
it's not as scary, I guess.
So yeah, looking forward
to using this.
This might be my new vlogging
setup, honestly.
Just how easy it is to pull
out and how less
straining it is for my arms
compared to carrying
the Sony FX3.
And yeah, let's see how I'll like
it by the end of this trip.
We are right now in Dasho-in or Daisho.
And it's a little bit noisy.
We're still very early,
but I found this little garden here
where there's a lot of small Buddha
or monk statues around.
A lovely little place, I would say.
So we just visited Daisho-in,
which is a temple here at Miyajima.
It's a lovely temple, a lot of cute
little Buddha statues
everywhere, and I definitely recommend
you guys to visit it.
Is that Sakura?
Oh, look.
Our first sakura over there.
We are, well, we're not that early
anymore here on Miyajima,
but it has been lovely with
less people around.
But of course, people are
starting to flood in
to the island.
I definitely recommend if you're
going to visit here,
either stay overnight on the island
or make the early morning journey.
Maybe even the first ferry
if your hardcore.
We are on top of the final stop
of the ropeway cable.
So at the, I think called Shi-Shi iwa
Observatory right now.
And we've got a great view over
the Miyajima Island
and the surrounding small islands,
and I think the mainland as well.
It's snowing up here.
It is not that cold, a little bit
chilly, enough for snow.
The view is quite astounding,
I would say.
You can just see those small islands,
small boats and ships.
Pretty nice, glad to be up here.
We weren't able to do this on our
first trip to Hiroshima.
So I'm glad that we were able
to do it this time.
The lemon's okay, but the red
bean and the custard
are the best in my opinion.
I'm not usually an oyster kind of
guy, but it's all right.
This is all right.
So that was our last day
here in Hiroshima.
We are heading to our next destination.
We're heading to Kinosaki Onsen now
for a, I guess, a more relaxing
kind of time.
We're having an early train to Kinosaki.
I finally feel like this trip, compared
to the last trip,
we sort of had the more complete
experience of the city.
There's not a lot of things
to do in Hiroshima,
but there's definitely a few key
things like the peace park,
the museums, Miyajima Island,
and of course the Okonomiyaki Village.
But yeah, I'm glad that we had
the chance to come back
and explore properly.
Now it's time to move on and
head to an onsen
and try to relax a little bit
before a more hectic schedule
in Kyoto and Tokyo.
But anyways, see you guys
in the next one.
Hey, what's up everyone?
It's Allan.
Thanks for watching the video.
I've got more Japan content
coming your way soon,
so stay tuned.
I also wanted to take this
opportunity to share
that I've recently soft launched YouTube
channel memberships.
If you'd like to support
me and the channel
a little bit more directly, this
is a great way to do it.
In addition to the standard
perks like badges
next to your name, as a small thank you,
members will get access to my
Custom Google maps,
the same ones that I've used
personally on trips
to places like Japan, Iceland,
and South Korea.
These maps are filled with pinned spots,
restaurants, activities, sites, and more,
all neatly organized into a travel
itinerary package.
Right now you'll find five maps available
and I'll be adding more in
the near future.
If you have any suggestions
for membership perks
that I should add, let me know
in the comments below.
I'd love to hear them.
I'm also planning some member
exclusive content,
maybe even stuff that's a little
outside the scope
of this channel, but I think
it might fit in there
or be worth sharing.
But you know, if you have
any ideas yet again,
let me know what do you guys want to see.
I'm all ears.
But anyway, thanks again for your time.
I truly appreciate the support.
This is Allan.
I'll see you guys in the next one.